{
    "id": "04db8139ae7c4c218dcfc488474c25fa",
    "title": "So, for and to",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "880fd03ce8f84884bf969ff8854954ea",
            "title": "So, For And Too",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Susie talked to the girl …………………. that she wouldn’t feel left out.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We are going there …………………. finalize the contract.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "An altimeter is used ………………. measure height above sea level.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will take it back to the shop ………………… get a replacement.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "so",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will need the car ………………… you will have to take a taxi.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Send the letter by speed post ………………… that she will get it before Tuesday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "so",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We stopped at the pub ………………….. a drink.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "so",
                        "to",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "A barometer is used …………………. measuring atmospheric pressure.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "People often go traveling ……………….. find themselves.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to",
                        "so"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Take some fruit ………………… eat on the way.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}